# **DIMITRIS RAMMOS**

# SOFTWARE ENGINEER

jrammos@outlook.com.gr +30 6940870953 Athens, Greece

<u>LinkedIn Profile</u> <u>GitHub</u> <u>My Portfolio</u>

# **Profile Summary**

I am a 22-year-old Junior Software Developer based in Athens, currently working at Entersoft. I am also an undergraduate student in the Department of Informatics and Telecommunications at the University of Athens. I have a strong interest in programming and web development. In the future, I aspire to work in fields such as artificial intelligence and cybersecurity. You can learn more about me and my projects by visiting My Portfolio.

#### Skills

- C/C++
- Rust
- Python

- MySQL
- Assembly

- C#
- Java
- HTML/CSS/JavaScript
- Git
- Agile

#### **Education**

#### **Department of Informatics and Telecommunications, NKUA**

OCT 2019-PRESENT

You can read about the department here

# **Work Experience**

#### Junior Software Developer - Entersoft

SEP 2023 - PRESENT

- I work as a Mobile developer and I coding C# .Net for cross applications( xamarin.ios, xamarin.forms and .Net Maui).
- The applications we develop are for Android, IOS and Windows.

### Junior Software Developer - Netcompany Intrasoft

FEB 2023 - SEP 2023

- I worked as a Full Stack developer and I coded Java, with Spring framework and primefaces. The project was the medical file and other many services for hospitals.
- Some of the technologies I used was WebLogic Server, Toad Database, SoapUI, Postman, Jenkins and Arifactory.

## **Associate Software Engineer - Wappier**

AUG 2022 - FEB 2023

- I worked as a Backend developer and I coded with Rust. I used the Axum framework from the Tokio library
- Some of the technologies I used with Rust was GraphQl, Kafka, Docker, Redis, MongoDB, PostgresDB, Prometheus, Grafana and Postman
- I have experience programming and developing software with teams implementing Agile methodologies.

#### Check-In Agent - Goldair Handling

JUL 2021 - SEP 2021

I was Check-In Agent for Aegean Airlines

#### Languages

- Greek
- English

#### **Hobbies**

• Gym

Running

Box

Trips